http://www.lydallautomotive.com/privacy-policy/

Lydall Thermal Acoustical Solutions
Other Lydall Sites
Lydall, Inc.
Privacy Policy
Lydall, Inc. (collectively, with its direct and indirect subsidiaries, worldwide, hereinafter "Lydall") is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to its Web site. This Privacy Policy and the accompanying Terms of Use describe the information collected by Lydall.com, how that information is used by Lydall, and the terms and conditions of your use of this site. We encourage you to read both of these documents carefully before using this site. If you have any comments or questions, or if there are other things we can do to maximize the value of this site to you, please contact our Legal Department at (860) 646-1233 or via email at info@lydall.com.
In General
You can visit our Web site without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information.  Lydall monitors user traffic patterns throughout the site according to a user's domain name, browser type, date and time of access, and pages viewed.  Our Web servers collect the domain names but not the e-mail addresses of visitors.  This information is collected in order to measure the number of visitors to our site and to determine which areas of the site users find useful based upon the amount of traffic to particular areas.  Lydall uses this information to enhance users' experience at the site and to better prepare future content based on the interests of users.
On occasion, a visitor to our Web site may be asked to provide personal information.  In most cases, personal information is used only to respond to inquiries.  Lydall will not provide e-mail addresses or other visitor information to any non-Lydall organization or partner.  In some instances, Lydall may provide links to non-Lydall controlled Web sites.  However, Lydall does not control such third-party Web sites, and cannot be responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by other sites.
Cookies
Lydall may use cookies on this site. Cookies are small text files sent to and stored on users' computers that allow Web sites, such as Lydall.com, to recognize repeat users, facilitate users' access to sites, and allow sites to compile aggregate data that will allow content improvements.  Cookies do not damage users' computers or files.  If users do not want cookies to be accessible by Lydall, most browser programs allow users to deny or disable the use of cookies.
Correcting / Changing Information
Lydall allows users to correct or change information submitted to Lydall or to report problems with the site or to pose questions or concerns by contacting us at info@lydall.com.
As Lydall expands and improves this site, we will endeavor to refresh this policy.  We encourage you to refer to this policy on a regular basis for updates to the policy.  This policy may be modified from time to time without prior notice to its users. Please notify us at info@lydall.com if you wish to remove your information from this site.
Copyright © 2011-2014 Lydall, Inc., Manchester, CT.  All rights reserved.
